[{"answer": " What do you want for Christmas", "docId": "Deep-Cover.txt", "asentId": 3, "question": " You don't know?? You gotta know what you want, boy, if you ever expect to get it", "qsentId": 2}, {"answer": "What were you doing with those kids", "docId": "Deep-Cover.txt", "asentId": 5, "question": " Your mom lets you play with them", "qsentId": 4}, {"answer": "Rush it, please. I want art, my friend, not reality. Budget hearings start in April, and I need my friend by then. They won't give us funding for three ounce buys", "docId": "Deep-Cover.txt", "asentId": 7, "question": "Without funding, we aren't doing it at all", "qsentId": 6}, {"answer": " You go to the Mexican place over there, and get the chicken tostada or the beef and bean burrito or both. And a milk", "docId": "Deep-Cover.txt", "asentId": 9, "question": " You get the milk! And get something for your mother, too.  What do you want", "qsentId": 8}, {"answer": "Another twent", "docId": "Deep-Cover.txt", "asentId": 11, "question": " A hundred??? my friend..", "qsentId": 10}, {"answer": "I don't dig white women.  Even if I did, it wouldn't mean the same thing", "docId": "Deep-Cover.txt", "asentId": 13, "question": "my friend. Who the fuck is my friend? Some smar", "qsentId": 12}, {"answer": "What", "docId": "Deep-Cover.txt", "asentId": 15, "question": " I miss you, too, Daddy..", "qsentId": 14}, {"answer": " How're we coming on my friend", "docId": "Deep-Cover.txt", "asentId": 17, "question": "Then you've got to", "qsentId": 16}, {"answer": "He supplies my friend. To get to him we'll have to take quantity", "docId": "Deep-Cover.txt", "asentId": 19, "question": "That's what killing Ivy did. I'll get to him soon", "qsentId": 18}, {"answer": " I'll get him something. Give me ten days, and I'll get him my friend on a plate", "docId": "Deep-Cover.txt", "asentId": 21, "question": "my friend, what are you telling me? I need my friend... and my friend. You arrest them, and you're throwing away everything I've set up", "qsentId": 20}, {"answer": "Where the hell is all the money? We're still a million short", "docId": "Deep-Cover.txt", "asentId": 23, "question": "my friend, we've got thirt", "qsentId": 22}, {"answer": " Coming in where", "docId": "Deep-Cover.txt", "asentId": 25, "question": " I'm going to have my friend in two days", "qsentId": 24}, {"answer": "Tell you what", "docId": "Deep-Cover.txt", "asentId": 27, "question": "What did I come to say", "qsentId": 26}, {"answer": "They're my children. They live in that place with their mother. I'm divorced from her. I haven't seen them in... some time. I want to, but I haven't been able to arrange it", "docId": "Deep-Cover.txt", "asentId": 29, "question": " Everything else... Everything else is... I don't know", "qsentId": 28}, {"answer": "Do it", "docId": "Deep-Cover.txt", "asentId": 31, "question": " Money? I got money..", "qsentId": 30}, {"answer": " You wouldn't even look at me", "docId": "Deep-Cover.txt", "asentId": 33, "question": "No, I wasn't, I was..", "qsentId": 32}]